## Madhavi Kagada

As a Junior Power Bi Developer, I created and created reports that offer insights that help customers make better decisions. BI tools in general, and Power BI in particular, were worked on in terms of business intelligence, data integration, data warehousing, modelling, databases, and technological issues.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Fortray Technology London, United Kingdom

Education technology startup with 50+ employees and \$100m+ annual revenue

Powerbi/Data Analyst

01/2023 - Present

- Experience work with Microsoft powerbi tolls(SSIS,SSAS)
- Conducted 80+ complex business problem analyses to reduce operational and financial risk.
- Developed 85% custom Microsoft Power BI dashboards, REPORTS visualizations, and interfaces with Microsoft SSRS to deliver meaningful and actionable insights
- Delivered 100% assigned tasks within the agreed budget.
- Store, organized and extract data by creating data warehouse using SQL Database and Excel.

### Greencore Company London, United Kingdom

Quality Process Analyst (Contact work)

04/2022 - 01/2023

- Improved customer retention by creating a personalized statistical formula for 950+ clients; grew monthly sales by 71% using complex formulas.
- Designed a comprehensive template that streamlined the billing process and helped slash annual overhead costs by 39%.
- Overhauled the company's legacy code per W3C standards, which added 84%to system capacity and cut \$3500 from the monthly operating costs.

## Evolution Infosystem, India

IT COMPANY

**Business Marketing Data Analyst** 

11/2020 - 01/2021

- Designed a database to track purchase orders, invoices, and shipping information from 1350+ clients.
- Devised and implemented an email package that automatically notifies 150+ developers about issues with overnight backups within 10 seconds of the incident. Created charts and graphs to visualize key metrics for management report and work with team
- Managed a 5-member cross-functional (product, engineering, sales, support) team and coordinated with six business partners toward the successful launch of an e-commerce platform.
- Conducted in depth marketing data analysis using 20+ statistical technicians and data visualization tools to identify trends.

#### **PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE**

# Marketing Analyst, Riyom Infotech ,India Data Analyst (Internship), University of Essex, United Kingdom

## 03/2018 - 03/2020 01/2022- 01/2023

#### **CONTACT**

- · Stratford, United Kingdom
- ·+44 7438752935
- · madhvikagada@gmail.com

#### **SKILLS**

#### Programming:

- Python
- · SSAS,SSIS,SSRS
- · R
- · ETL(Extract, Transform, Load)
- Data Analysis

#### Tools and Software:

- · Microsoft SQL
- Power Bi
- Python
- · Tableau

#### Languages:

· English

#### **EDUCATION**

Univeísity of Essex, UK -Applied Data Science – 2023

Gujarat Technical University -Bachelor of Computer Engineering - 2018

#### **OTHER**

- IBM Certified
   Data analyst with
   Python
- Google certified Data Analyst
- Power BI Data
   Visualization and
   Dashboard Tips,
   Tricks, &
   Techniques by
   UDEMY